Deepika chandel (1) Featured

Java Developer seeking roles in Software Development, Application
Programming, Requirement Gathering, System Analysis, Project Management, Product
Development, Eclipse, Hibernate, HTML, CSS, Javascript, MySQL



Current Designation: Software Engineer Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 5 Month(s)

Current Company: Serosoft Solutions Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Current Location: Indore Highest Degree: MCA [Computers]

Pref. Location: Mumbai, Pune, Indore

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Java Developer, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Requirement

Gathering, System Analysis, Project Management, Product Development, Eclipse, Hibernate, HTML, CSS, Javascript, MySQL

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

Nearly 4.5 years of experience in Java development, Product Development and Project Management. Hands on Experience in JSE, JEE, Spring 3.0, Hibernate, JavaScript ,AJAX,MYSQL Knowledge of Eclipse and Netbeans tool for the development of Java projects. Hands on experience Tomcat server Ability to communicate effectively with team member and with clients Hands on experience on relational database system like MYSQL

Work Experience

Serosoft Solutions as Software Engineer Jun 2018 to Till Date

Serosoft private limited as Software Developer Jun 2018 to Sep 2020

Advanz101 system private limited as Java Developer Apr 2016 to Apr 2018

Tridents technologies India private limited as Trainee Java Developer Jan 2015 to Jun 2015

Education

UG: B.Sc (Computers) from Rani Durgavati Vishwavidyalaya (RDVV), Jabalpur in 2012

PG: MCA (Computers) from Rajiv Gandhi Proudyogiki Vishwavidyalaya (RGPV), Bhopal in 2015

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Us	Ised Experience	
Windows, Linux(ubuntu 14.0)			
JSE,JEE			
HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT			
MySQL			
Tomcat			
Hibernate			
Spring			
Edit plus, Notepad.			
Eclipse, NetBeans			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				

Affirmative Action

Category: General

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time